{
    "subject": "resource/Der_bewegte_Mann",
    "predicate": "property/editing",
    "object": "resource/Ueli_Christen",
    "human_readable": "Der bewegte Mann was edited by Ueli Christen.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.919338583946228,
            "question": "Who edited the film 'Der bewegte Mann'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.669897735118866,
            "question": "What is the name of the film that Ueli Christen edited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5926227569580078,
            "question": "When was 'Der bewegte Mann' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.585107684135437,
            "question": "Are there any other films edited by Ueli Christen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49314385652542114,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'Der bewegte Mann'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4805918037891388,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the film 'Der bewegte Mann'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.415983647108078,
            "question": "Who are the actors in 'Der bewegte Mann'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39600977301597595,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Der bewegte Mann' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3944156765937805,
            "question": "Is Ueli Christen a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3709496855735779,
            "question": "Where can I watch 'Der bewegte Mann'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Der bewegte Mann was edited by Ueli Christen.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6909_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ueli Christen a filmmaker?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6909_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'Der bewegte Mann' likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6909_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the actors in 'Der bewegte Mann'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6909_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6909_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6909_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6909_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6909_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6909_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6909_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6909_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6909_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6909_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6909_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not contain any information that supports the statement that \"Der bewegte Mann\" was edited by Ueli Christen. Ueli Christen is mentioned in one of the documents, but his role is described as an editor and assistant director for other films, not \"Der bewegte Mann.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Ueli Christen was an editor and assistant director, not the editor of Der Bewegte Mann. He has worked on other films as editor, but there's no information provided that he edited Der Bewegte Mann specifically.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Ueli Christen's involvement with Der Bewegte Mann in any of the provided context information.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because there is no information provided about Ueli Christen being involved with editing \"Der bewegte Mann\", only that he was born on 21 April 1962 and is an editor and assistant director known for other films.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention Ueli Christen as an editor of Der bewegte Mann. Instead, it provides details about Ralf K\u00f6nig, the creator of the comic strip that inspired the film, and Ueli Christen, who is described as an editor and assistant director with credits in different films.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}